



CHE QUANG HUY

Phone: 0939.260.508

Email: chequanghuybtt@gmail.com **Portfolio:** huycheportfolio.vercel.app GitHub: github.com/chequanghuyca

SUMMARY

I'm a Full-stack Software Engineer with 2.5 years of experience in Web Development. I have 2 year of experience in Full-stack ReactJS, NextJS, ThirdWeb, NestJS, NodeJS and 4 months of Spring-related technologies.

With my knowledge of ReactJS, NextJS, ThirdWeb, NestJS and NodeJS. I enjoy solving Front-end and Back-end problems and creating high-performance systems. I also spend time learning new technologies and best practices to become a better engineer.

EDUCATION

Ho Chi Minh City University of Technology - HCMUT, Ho Chi Minh.

2018 - 2023

Major: Computer Science.

Level: Junior

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programing Languages: JavaScript & TypeScript, Java, C/C++. Frameworks/Platforms:

- React[S, Next[S, Nest[S, Node]S, ThirdWeb.
- HTML5, CSS/SCSS, ES6, jQuery, Bootstrap, Tailwind.
- WebAPI, MessageQueue, ORM.

Management Systems: Micro Service, MVC.

Databas: Oracle, MySQL, PostgreSQL.

Other Technologies: Git, Redis, RabbitMQ, Docker, JWT.

Foreign Languages: Toeic 550

EXPERIENCE

Mirai Labs. Mar 2024 - Present Ho Chi Minh City

Front-end Developer

Project: Marketplace Petopia Games, Marketplace Pegaxy Games, Operator Mirai App.

- Description: Web systems used for creating marketplaces, buying, selling, exchanging, and auctioning. And operational system for the Mirai App.
- Technologies:
 - * Front-end: ReactJS, NestJS, ThirdWeb, JWT, Blockchain,...
- Responsibilities:
 - * Built a marketplace for buying, selling, and auctioning NFTs.
 - * Developed an operator web page for the Mirai App (similar to Binance).
 - * Worked on website optimization using SEO techniques. Worked on website optimization using SEO techniques.
 - * Integrated ThirdWeb for blockchain functionalities.

* Implemented web tokens and JWT for secure authentication.

Data and Information Technology Center of HCMUT.

Aug 2022 - Mar 2024

Full-stack Software Engineer

Ho Chi Minh City

- Project: Quality Assurance System.
- **Description:** The system for OISP to manage survey, statistics data, manage ISO goal for more than 100 staff of OISP and all lecturer, student of HCMUT.
- Technologies:
 - * Front-end: ReactJS, Redux, Bootstrap.
 - * Back-end: ExpressJS, Oracle, Redis, RabbitMQ.
- Responsibilities:
 - * Participate in analyzing, recording and clarifying the user's business requirements, giving suggestions and proposing solutions to design and deploy the system.
 - * Work directly with Tech Leader to determine the system's roadmap and tasks. Build features and improvements based on the roadmap. Provide weekly progress updates to OISP specialists.
 - * Participate in code reviews and provide constructive feedback to other developers on the team.
 - * Check and handle arising errors as well as optimize the system during operation.

FPT Software. May 2022 – Aug 2022

Back-end Engineer

Ho Chi Minh City

- **Project:** Human Resource Management Software.
- **Description:** Developing API for Human Resource Management Software.
- **Technologies:** Java SpringBoot.
- Responsibilities:
 - * Learn about Java and SpringBoot.
 - * Developing and maintaining API for Human Resource Management Software using SpringBoot and other related technologies.
 - * Participating in code reviews with leader and write reports on product features.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Binh Thanh Trung Portal.

Jun 2023 – Dec 2023

Full-stack Software Engineer

Ho Chi Minh City

- **Project:** Binh Thanh Trung Portal.
- **Description:** The online portal of Binh Thanh Trung Commune, features functions allowing residents to register procedures online. Employees are responsible for reviewing and printing the registered procedures.
- Technologies:
 - * Front-end: ReactJS, Redux, Bootstrap.
 - * Back-end: ExpressJS, PostgreSQL.
- Responsibilities:
 - * Responsible for the entire information portal project.
 - * Functions include procedure registration, verification, and sending notification emails.